We have a possibility to have a hover zone, so zone image is only off over the website,
simple hover your mouse, over the image to an object.
I'll add them by the other end, see how it works.
In the meantime, I will remove my click to remove element, because we already know about it.
So I'll remove the element, and hide that, and now we'll just use a hover zone.
Bring this by default, so activate its non-togo, and this tab we can disable it.
So, yeah, this way we can specify.
If I go to Amazon, activate hover zone, it will be, I'll press U, now save it.
So, now I can activate its working this way, but I think I will implement it a little bit differently.
Add another feature, so this is the blue web app.
We can test it to, it's like a smooth quick zone to, maybe I'll remove hover zone, but
it's like a smooth zone, and it has this extension, it was all like a zoom in, and even type
of monetization.
So right click, it's hard to zoom, where we see it, I will now pin it up, smooth zone,
and we'll add, so I'll hide it, see a blue web app, let me see the blue web app, how
it works, now I'm back here, so this is the blue web, this is a highlighting key, so I cannot
even use it, it's premium, it's 10,000 users, so product your sensitive data, we see some
key features, I will just add this as a new feature from my case, I want you to add a
blue area, blue area, I've got the blue, crown extension, up, up window, and here, the
blue, key area from an extension of a window, and new agent, settings for blue, and the
deck should be low in elements, and remove title elements, I guess I think the, I've
got the name, so I'll just quickly check it, so at the very top there is an element
hide the reversion, and title, very bottom, here's small font, and a version, alright,
so this one will add an extension, we have some available areas for it, so hide it's
not on the show is the domain page, now refresh it, okay, and now when I go back here,
I have a directly blue intensity, so separate domain, I'll just say I don't want to have
it at the top, and you have another visibility, so blue ones, I have it still I don't like
it, and okay, I'll just use it again, and I'll just say for blue area, and for settings,
I want to preview, and say so, we'll redact ends, okay, this is unknown, this is a just,
I'll just, I know it, okay, as I get, in the main, from extension window, I will add
another feature, and redact should be on it visible, not quite nice, correct, and element
of website, but the text itself, on name, I have to do this, this one is a bigger task
as well, but I'll tell you that I don't need to be ready to go, okay, see me, this is
done now, I had multiple changes, I'm going to actually preview errors, first I'll clear
all it, refresh it, go back here, check if my previous visibility is still working, some
blue ones, it's working, I think we need to face the picture, it's just not very well,
but we'll manage it later, hide ones, and have like persistent, you can clear it, now I've
selected area, since working, but I'll use maybe blur, okay, that's pretty much working,
so by the last thing I want, and after I release selecting area, it should stop selecting
part of the page, because it's option, we need to increase our selection part, so it
outdated code, so selection mode stops after releasing the mouse, make more livable colors,
they are too bright, so you can see this extension can be monetized, and last I will just
check that smooth zone, so right click with allow us to check smoothness, and hold the
zone right, what if I try to type it now, and I like the thing that we actually select
area, also in the Chrome extension, but there is button to cancel the selection, it shouldn't
be there, because it's closed by selecting, it should just allow us to select, and when
we release selection, it should stay still, and open a window to either change its visibility
or press, so return, and selecting it should close automatically Chrome, pop up, you
know, and last but not least what I am going to do, I will just press it here, and now
I will just use the smooth zone, actually I want to check it, so press hold the zone right
click, always follow up the cursor, this is the error click, I am not sure what is it,
maybe I can switch it, maybe it's, I think it's not right mouse button click, because
we see it will change, but I will switch to maybe hold, and if I press out, okay this
is the same like it works, maybe shift, I just need to go because I am still in that stupid
selection mode, and I will open new tab, I will try to add maybe my way, maybe I am
to stop it, do that extension, but I know what I want, so again if I go to extension, refresh
it, I am at hider, and now if I press it again select area, we see errors, hopefully
it will be the last one, copy, it can be time consuming, refresh, make extension, go back,
open new tab, open the select area, mark it, now it stays still, this is where I want
it, blur, and it's perfect, and sometimes it doesn't take all of the elements, but we
can fix it in one, in the previous elements here we can get visibility, I will just check
maybe how it looks for the article, so if I now remove that pattern, and select it again,
like here, now it works perfect, so this way we just blurred some of the parts, and we
can switch easily, and the last feature, I promise you will be the last, I want to have
like a mini zoom, because for example zoom in allows us to actually use like automatic
zoom, so polish and perfect, click to keyboard, haircut, among all zooming, and I like
this idea of simple tab, so I will just open new agent, new agents, I will paste it, I
want to have a function out there, that will allow me to zoom to certain part of website,
when I hold, for example, let me, I think the base will be left controlled, but I was to
change in the settings, with some other binding, in the settings we could have a zoom
amount and interpolation, smoothness, hopefully it will be enough, okay, now it should
be alright, I will refresh it, elements hider, and now when I go back again, I can see
if it actually works, I'll refresh it, it should have some hidden elements, and there
is smooth zoom, I think the extension is here, we could probably see a switch between
settings, selection, and settings, but now I can use zoom key, with control, and I have a
zoom key, that's perfect, this is what I wanted, it's very nice, and it's right to zoom
out page, give that you might not to press it fast, because otherwise it will lose some
of the functionality, but we just try to look for the page that you want to zoom, so if I
press this one, see if I go to now any page, this sounds terrible, I think, like the
commentary, I have image, I can press, probably sometimes it is not detecting the central
zoom works perfect, but I would like to get more precise and zoom to a car so place, it
usually seems to some other part of page, I want the position of the car, and open
new agent, and you put agent that is basically here, I have this website preview, I don't
want to have an address preview at the top right, because it just occupies the place,
there are others, and instead of this, add three tabs, one will be for ID elements, the
second about X plus zoom, let's add it, and the third will be settings, we could probably
obviously add the settings with that color directly from here, so I will move it from
now there, so try to now fix our visibility and then change the functionality, it seems to
be done, so this pop-up now users tap it state of the europere, and each tap contains
it's forever-counted users can switch between the hide-out-stop is active by default,
normally the car is found ready to test, open it now, and it's hide-out now try to zoom it,
to zoom for this at the very top of the bottom, so we have to go like this to zoom and the
table, okay, this one we can fix easily, and we have a zoom, right, elements, and settings,
this is what I wanted, we can even add some settings to suit between dark mode, but this
how our elements looks like, so it's perfect, now have an out, our check if it's possible,
and now it's now, the zoom settings we can use, change like a zoom amount to be five, so
now it will be even more closer, I think it's great, we can even try to restart the default
settings, especially here, so now if I press zoom, it's a little bit less, and this way we create
our own cursor system extension that we can monetize, such as zooming, right, so we can even
enough for like left and deal for a nice price.